ignitiondeck.com 2015-12-06

# Virtuous Giant & IgnitionDeck Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Virtuous Giant we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.

Virtuous Giant LLC (“Virtuous Giant”) operates several websites including virtuousgiant.com and ignitiondeck.com. It is Virtuous Giant’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Virtuous Giant collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Virtuous Giant’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Virtuous Giant’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Virtuous Giant may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Virtuous Giant also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and customers. Virtuous Giant only discloses logged in user and customer IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that purchaser IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the website.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Virtuous Giant’s websites choose to interact with Virtuous Giant in ways that require Virtuous Giant to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Virtuous Giant gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask IgnitionDeck customers to provide a username and email address in order to access our software. Those who engage in transactions with Virtuous Giant – by purchasing access to the IgnitionDeck plugin, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Virtuous Giant collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Virtuous Giant. Virtuous Giant does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Virtuous Giant may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Virtuous Giant may monitor login frequency to help identify active users. Virtuous Giant may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Virtuous Giant does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Virtuous Giant discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Virtuous Giant’s behalf or to provide services available at Virtuous Giant’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Virtuous Giant’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Virtuous Giant will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Virtuous Giant discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Virtuous Giant believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Virtuous Giant, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Virtuous Giant website and have supplied your email address, Virtuous Giant may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Virtuous Giant and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Virtuous Giant takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Virtuous Giant uses cookies to help Virtuous Giant identify and track visitors, their usage of Virtuous Giant website, and their website access preferences. Virtuous Giant visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Virtuous Giant’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Virtuous Giant’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Virtuous Giant, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Virtuous Giant goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Virtuous Giant may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Virtuous Giant and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Virtuous Giant may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Virtuous Giant’s sole discretion. Virtuous Giant encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Supporter Wall

The supporter wall displays buyer avatars collected from one of the following sources (Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Gravatar). This avatar is generated by matching buyer usernames with publicly available images. Wwe do not display username, email, or profile information. Should you wish to have your image removed from our supporter wall, please send an email to hello@virtuousgiant.com with said request and we will remove your image in a timely fashion.
